[Music]
n half of my heart is
in my heart is
[Music]
inana
oh n hey half my heart is in a n he took
me back to e
Atlanta oh but my heart is in a there
something about man yeah he didn't walk
up how you doing when he came in said
lot of girl do it but I
came in a
minute
Summer's got him
got feel
like I
KN
I
like and then I had to tell I had
[Music]
to my heart is
in he took me back to East Atlanta n n
oh my heart is in her my heart is in
her I knew it was there when I the signs
welcome to I when H from behind it me
every time but in the street he
said my daddy me he
got and then I had to tell him I had to
go oh n n n n
my heart is
in took me
back oh no my heart is in my heart is
[Music]
in my heart is in the
[Applause]
never say it's over if I'm breathing
ring to the Moonlight and I'm SP headed
to the Stars ready to go f start
walking don't never say it's so I'm
breathing to the Moonlight and I'm
speeding I'm headed to the
Stars miss high I know that I'm mying
for life that I don't need all never Len
to replies learn a lesson from the wise
you should never take advice from
somebody that
ain't said I would make it out a li they
told me I would never see the rise
that's why I got to do it every
time
Brea
the I'm headed to ready to I'm start
walking don't never say it's over if I'm
breathing racing to the Moonlight and
I'm speeding I'm headed to the
[Applause]
[Music]
to said I want to make it out of make it
out
of told me I never see the r never see
the
r breathing to the light and I'm
SP to ready to
[Music]
[Applause]
well I got I could do something from the
album if you
want
come David what about if I did crumble
could you do uh I won't crumble with
you now this is a very important song so
I tried to pick songs that mean a lot to
me and this song is trying to tell you
people that you love you know sometimes
they need to be backed up and you need
to sort of give them strength and and
encouragement so that's what this song
means you know I'll do anything for you
but I won't crumble with you if you fall
you know it's a serious song but I'll do
it if you if you would like me to do it
I
will we would love it
song Let me see if I can hear
this I will
wake in the
morning if you
call I stand beside you as long as I
can
I will hold
back the
evening of your
son but I won't
crumble with
you if you
fall come walk with me and
hold to my
hand touch
be let me know I ain't here by
myself stretch my night
dreams
into my
day stop short of
falling
apart if I go
down I will
wait in the
morning if you
call I'll stand beside
you as long as I
can I will hold
back the
evening of your
son but I won don't
crumble with
you if you
[Music]
[Applause]
fall
wow thank you
David
I think that was one of the best moments
of my life oh that was so special thank
you what special song Yeah well my wife
you know she she was dying of lung
cancer so I said you know I I was always
able to fix stuff you know I was always
I was always able to you know to do
things if if she needed me for anything
I was always there but uh she said you
can't crumble with me don't fall with me
now you've done everything you can you
must carry on you know and do what you
do so that's what the song when I heard
it I thought my God this this thing is
is like it was written for this
situation yeah it's a lovely song thanks
for sharing that with us Tom
oh
yeah oh leave then you
start sometimes late at night
[Music]
night I lie awake and watch her sleeping
fling Just
sh she's lost in peaceful dreams so I
turn out the lights and lay there in the
dark
please and a thought crosses my
mind I'm never wake in the morning
love you brother love you love you I
love you I love you she ever doubt the
way I feel about her in my
heart
woo If
Tomorrow Never
Comes would you know how much I
love and did I try in every way to show
her every day she's my
only it's my time Earth
[Music]
through she must face this world with
I is the love I gave her in the past
going to be enough to last
tomorrow
never come
come on I love you so much you I'm happy
you're here I
love oh
me
yeah I feel so
unprepared what what are you doing I'm
I'm checking to see I'm get to get the
front row seat you about to sing oh I
don't know what I'mma sing I want to
sing Impossible Dream Dave
[Music]
that's how to
run where the brave then I
go got
[Applause]
r
you're in to from
AOSS to
try when you're un tattoo we
breae
to the
[Music]
unreachable this is my
CR to I love that
star no matter how
hopess no matter how
far to
free the honoring
[Applause]
of
[Music]
they say oh my God I see the way you
shine take your hand my
de you know you stopped me dead when I
was passing
by and now I pray to see you dance just
one more time so I Sayce dance
dancebody
do they sing for me for me for
me and when you're down I'll make it do
all again oh I see you see you see you
everything
down and you know I I I like your
style you make me make me make me to
cry and now back to see you Dan just one
more time give it to
my
yeah your hands
up
go down hey now now late on down around
move it all
around
like dance dance
dance
never seen anybody do
seen for me for
me
[Music]
i' got on a stream sitting on the
rainbow got a string around
my what
alive can't you see I'm in
love come on
[Music]
baby
sing
anytime I move my
finger me can't you see how me
love life is a beautiful place beautiful
way as long as I hold a string I got a
Str I'll be SE so and
so if I should ever let it
go I've got the world of the stre
sting on the
rainbow got a string around my
finger what a love
Li what
a what a love for CU I'm in
love love baby I'm in
love
hold
come
[Music]
on well I need to hear you sing a little
bit of Ordinary People come on
oh okay maybe I'll come sing with you
what do you think oh
my oh my God he's pulling out the big
guns I feel like I lost
already
people we don't know which way to go
we orinary
people BBE we take it slow take it
slow slow thank you n
dad can I be on team NES and team Legend
right now I feel like man sign me up go
ahead CH John just did so much uh I'll
sing ordinary people with you
too if you want to you want me to let's
go what is happening I don't know I'm
here for it best John Legend
impersonation let's
go we're just orinary people he can sing
chess can
sing BBE we should take it slow take it
[Music]
slow this time will take
it's
slow
wa sound amazing that was awesome that
was awesome can't do nothing about it
wow what a crazy moment a raer they call
him the rapper but he's also a singer I
thought there was no hope but now I feel
like chance might have a
chance
Megan I've got a bone to pick with
Megan
no because Dear Future Husband it sounds
like my song dancing me
tonight I remember when it came out I
was like this sounds
familiar I thought the same thing
honestly it's a great song we should
sing a little bit now we should do a d
you start it and I'll comeing for the
chorus I just W
to you guys need microphone microphones
yeah yet but I'm sitting down I'm not as
cool as Tom Jones
[Music]
You Dear Future
Husband here's a few things you need to
know if you want to be my one and
only
oh my
[Music]
life oh here it comes
yeah I'm going to come in yall ready for
this you know this
[Music]
one take me on a day I deserve a b and
don't forget the flowers every
anniversary cuz if you treat me right
I'll be the perfect wife groceries bu
what you need you got to know how to
treat me like a
lady even when I'm acting crazy tell me
everything's all right
tell them I just
to come on
baby I just want you to dance with me
tonight you know it to come on feel your
husband make bab lonely I just want you
to dance with me tonight tonight oh
God did we do it we have to keep we just
keep going you verse sing your song two
I my name is nice to meet you can I tell
your baby I looked around there's a
whole lot of sexy ladies but none like
you you shout so bright hey yeah yeah
yeah and I was wondering if you I me
spend a minute on the floor of Clos
getting lost in it I won't give up
without a you
say I just
oo G
baby I just want you to dance with
me
tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
mama just killed a
man put a g against his head P my
trigger now he's
dead oh mama
[Applause]
life had just
begun but now I've gone and through it
all
way
[Music]
Mama didn't mean to make you
cry if I'm not back again this time
tomorrow carry on carry on
as if nothing really
[Music]
matter I see a little silou of a
man are very very frightening me
[Music]
I'm just a poor boy nobody loves me he's
just a poor boy from
aor his from
his me for me for
[Applause]
me
so you think you can stall me and spit
in my
eyes so you think you can love me and
leave me to
die
oh
baby down to me
baby just got to get out just got to get
out out of
[Music]
here oh yeah oh oh
[Applause]
yeah nothing really
matter and anyone can
see nothing really
matters
nothing really
to
[Applause]
[Music]
me I've been reading books of old the
Legends and the m aill and his gold
Hercules and ESC Spiderman's control and
bman with his fist
and clearly I don't see myself upon that
L but she said where you want to go how
much you want to risk I'm not looking
for somebody with some super human gift
some super hero some fairy tale Bliss
just something I can turn to somebody I
can kiss I want something just like
this do do do do do do I want something
just like this do
do
do uhuh I want something just like this
we change with the Tes sometimes I'm
proud sometimes I swallow Pride
sometimes it rain sometimes above the
clouds but never doubt I want something
just like this and face is going to pass
and though I get eager my patience going
to last what feels like forever I'm
saying it goes fast but what Blas where
do you want to go how much you want to
risk I'm not looking for somebody with
some super human gifts some
superhero fairy
tale just something I can turn to
somebody I can kiss I want something
just like
[Music]
this
[Applause]
I want something just like
this oh I want something this like
this oh I if you want to go I want you
I'm look you
with oh I
superer just something I to somebody I
or I want something just like
[Music]
[Applause]
this
[Music]
fore
for
[Music]
Fore
fore
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
white shirt now R my blood
nose
slipping you on my T
toes
ging like nobody
knows thinking you are so creaming
BR
hum when you don't say thank you please
I do what I want what I want to do
my so you
like just get just
a have the bad time make you my S time
make you
make
it my
[Music]
bre I like it when you take control even
and you know that You Don't Own Me I let
you play the role I'll be your
animal my mind relax to sing along me
but she won't sing the song she resol
that lyrics be that man I
know so
[Music]
[Applause]
you're
I'm what can I say
the
the bad guy the bad
[Music]
[Applause]
guy
we are B guy
ever with love
is
[Applause]
yeah from sah
love
okay that
[Music]
is yeah wow wow wow wow wow
[Applause]
wow
for so many years we were friends and
yes I always knew what we could
do so many tears in the rainf the night
you said that love had come to you I
thought you were never my kind I thought
that I could never feel for you you the
passion love you feeling and so you
for someone
new now that you
away I'm stand
[Music]
my
Sarah she got the love she is dreaming
of never find the words to say but I
know that today she's going to send her
letter to you from s love
W the pictures to the
stars and the
is she get for you so don't make up blue
when she rites to you from
Sarah
[Music]
love from Santos from Johannes from Mark
inla she's in
Superstition black cats dogs I feel
premonition that girl's going to make me
fall she's in the New Sensations new
kicks in the candle light she's I do
addiction for every day at night make
you take your clothes I found daning in
the r she make you live her crazy life
but she take away your pain like a bu to
the come
on upside Inside Out living the Loc
will sh P you down
living lips
are
and she will you out
Liv
living she's
living woke up right here in Australia
in a pet chip town she took my heart and
she took my money she must just live
sing drinks water makes
[Applause]
you
you never be the same make you go
[Applause]
inside p p you
down lips are de and skin your color of
Moa she will wear you out
[Music]
[Applause]
Liv come
on make
take Dan
in break you with a Crazy Life she take
away your
[Applause]
to
your
[Applause]
sh P you
[Music]
down
she you
[Applause]
living
[Music]
if you could see anybody battle anybody
in the world who would you
pick I would I would love to see you and
Jennifer have a battle I can't battle on
top that wouldn't be a
battle I can't battle no
time thanks a
lot we don't have
anything on right
come on well I mean if we did this is a
man's world but I mean if if we did it
we'd have to I have to follow
you oh my God I'm following you T cuz
it's the man's what what key would be
would be it that is suffice
[Music]
for this is a main world
a world this is a man world don't you
know man world yes a know be but it
Ain a
woman a
[Applause]
girl man made a little bitty baby girl
and a baby boy yeah he did man made them
happy happy cuz a man made them
toys and after a man makes everything
everything everything everything don't
you know then tell me what about it oh
yeah man made what money yes he did to
buy from other men oh
[Music]
oh is
world but it ain't
[Music]
[Applause]
that this is the m world don't you know
thank
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
breaking down C back they just have to
go cuz they don't know where and all I
want to he is the message be my dreams
the go long asep
now we we for the land down forever and
in take it only on your
St is and falling down love forever love
as feeling can forever you and me
wind wind
for is
[Music]
[Applause]
everybody
[Music]
[Applause]
foree
we we for the land god forever and
we all on
your it is B
fall love
forever fre done forever you and me
women women fall land
everybody
[Music]
[Applause]
Coe
[Music]
foree
[Applause]
[Music]
foring with me
with
[Music]
[Applause]
fore
[Music]
the fans at want you to sing
2002 she's doing it she do it yeah I
just think I just need the
k i I will
always
[Music]
yes I will always
remember kiss my lips
Fe and it went just like this no it's
never been better than the
summer of
[Music]
2002 we were only
11 but acting like one UPS like we are
in a
present drinking from plastic cups
singing Love is forever and
never well I guess that was
true o
W dancing on the hood in the middle of w
my where we s all our childhood friends
and it went like this
[Applause]
daying hold up if you want to go with me
hit me baby one more
time for you and me on the days when we
were young singing at the top of both
our
[Applause]
[Music]
day on the
day on the day we in
Love on the day we in love love
love yeah
nice
[Music]
yeah
sh
no
[Music]
[Applause]
my
[Music]
Planet should the m
to
[Music]
[Applause]
the
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
Fore
okay
[Music]
how's it
get
[Music]
dealer
hey
[Music]
the
planet the m
[Music]
[Applause]
you're just too good to be true can't
take my eyes off of you you be like
having to touch I want to hold you so
much that long last love has arrived and
I thank God I'm alive you're just too
good to be true can't take my eyes off
you I need you
baby if it's quite all right I need you
baby to warn the lonely night I love
love you
baby trust in me when I say it's
okay oh pretty
baby don't let me down I pray oh pretty
baby now that I found you stay and let
me love you oh baby let me love you oh
baby
[Music]
hey you're just too good to be true then
take my eyes off of you you be like
heaven to touch and I want to hold you
so much had long last love as a rap and
I thank God I'm alive you're just too
good to be true can't take my eyes over
you I need you
baby and if it's
all right I need you
baby to warm the lonely night I love you
baby trust in me when I say it's
okay yay oh pretty
baby don't let me down I pray oh pretty
baby Now That I Found You Stay let you
love love you
baby let me love
[Music]
you
hey it so nice to have you around my
house yeah I was like that L
like teach me your
[Music]
wish
is it getting
better do you feel the
same will it make it easier on you
now you got someone to
blame you say
one one
life when it's one
need in the night
one love we got to share
it and it leaves you
darling if you don't
[Applause]
care for
it
[Music]
yeah did I disappoint
you leave a bad taste in your mouth
you act like you never had
[Music]
love you want me to go
without well it's too
late
tonight to drag the paast down into the
light we're W but we're not the same we
got to carry each other carry each
other
[Music]
W you say love is a temple love is a
high love is a temple love is a
high you ask me to enter but then you
make me CW but I can keep hold hold on
to what you got cuz all you got is
her one
love one
blood one life you got to do what you
[Applause]
should more
life with each
other sister and
my one life but we're not the the same
we got to carry each other carry each
[Music]
other
I can feel it coming in the air
[Applause]
tonight oh
Lord and I've been waiting for this
moment for all my
life oh
Lord Can you feel it coming in the air
tonight
[Music]
oh well I
remember I remember don't
worry how could I ever forget
it's the first
time the last time we ever
met but I know the reason why you keep
your silence up oh no you don't fool
me cuz the hurt doesn't
show but the pain to grow it's no
stranger to you and
[Music]
me I can
feel in the I can feel
it I've been waiting for this
for all my well I've been waiting on my
life you
[Music]
feeling
[Applause]
you can you feel it
in the
air and I just can't help Ling
[Applause]
[Music]
you